A Finding Aid to the Susan Conway Gallery Records, circa 1928, circa 1940s-2003, bulk 1987-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.susacong
Archives of American Art
Susan Conway Gallery records
circa 1928, 1940s-2003
bulk 1987-2003
AAA.susacong
Archives of American Art
23.9 Linear feet
The modern and contemporary art gallery records of the Susan Conway Gallery in Washington, D.C. measure 23.9 linear feet and date from circa 1928, circa 1940s-2003, with the bulk of the material dating from 1987-2003. Nearly half of the collection documents the gallery’s work as the sole representative of artist and political cartoonist Pat Oliphant through administrative records, exhibition files, press clippings, and a handful of photographs. Also found in the collection are artists’ files of other artists represented by the gallery, client files, administrative records, printed materials, and the records of the Susan Conway Conservation Studio.
Susan Conway Gallery (Washington, D.C.).
Scope and Contents note
The modern and contemporary art gallery records of the Susan Conway Gallery in Washington, D.C. measure 23.9 linear feet and date from circa 1928, circa 1940s-2003, with the bulk of the material dating from 1987-2003. Nearly half of the collection documents the gallery’s work as the sole representative of artist and political cartoonist Pat Oliphant through administrative records, exhibition files, press clippings, and a handful of photographs. Also found in the collection are artists’ files of other artists represented by the gallery, client files, administrative records, printed materials, and the records of the Susan Conway Conservation Studio.
The exhibitions and sales of artwork by artists represented by the gallery are documented through biographies, correspondence, exhibition printed materials, newspaper clippings, notes, price lists, photographs and slides, sales invoices, and shipping records. Artists of interest include Eric Aho, Will Barnet, Leonard Baskin, Dorothy Dehner, Mary Ellen Doyle, Brece Honeycutt, Ross M. Merrill, Otto and Gertrud Natzler, Sam Scott and Edward Sorel. Sales records can also be found in Client Files, along with correspondence with individual clients and galleries, notes, and shipping records.
Nearly half of the collection documents the exhibitions, loans, promotion and sales of Patrick Oliphant’s artwork. Materials found include contracts, correspondence with galleries, museums, and clients, exhibition printed materials, notes, scattered photographs, price lists, proposals, sales invoices, and shipping records. Much of the material relates to Oliphant’s numerous traveling exhibitions, including "Oliphant: The New World Order in Drawing and Sculpture," “Oliphant’s Presidents: 25 Years of Caricatures,” and “Seven Presidents.”
Administrative and Miscellaneous Records includes records related to the daily operation of the gallery space and promotion of the gallery, such as contracts, a guest book, documents created for Conway’s public talks, scattered documentation regarding gifts of artwork, and other miscellaneous records.
The bulk of the printed materials are Susan Conway Gallery exhibition announcements. Also found are some catalogs, clippings and a brochure. The records of the Susan Conway Conservation Studio include condition reports, correspondence with clients, notes, and photographs and slides of artwork.
None of the gallery records of the Santa Fe location are included in this collection. The outlying dates of this collection include older photographs and a negative found in the Artists’ Files.
Arrangement note
The collection is arranged as 7 series.
Series 1: Artists’ Files, circa 1928, circa 1940s-2003 (7.6 linear feet; Boxes 1-8, 26, OV 27)
Series 2: Client Files, 1987-2003 (1.85 linear feet; Boxes 8-10, 26)
Series 3: Exhibition and Loan Files, 1987-2003 (0.85 linear feet; Boxes 10-11)
Series 4: Records Regarding Patrick Oliphant, 1976-2003 (11.5 linear feet; Boxes 11-22, 26, OV 27)
Series 5: Administrative and Miscellaneous Records, 1978-2003 (0.5 linear feet; Box 22)
Series 6: Printed Materials, 1987-2002 (0.4 linear feet; Box 23, OV 27)
Series 7: Susan Conway Conservation Studio Records, before 1970s-1993 (1.2 linear feet; Boxes 23-26)
Biographical/Historical note
The Susan Conway Gallery was founded by Susan Conway in the Georgetown neighborhood of Washington, D.C. in 1987. In 1991, the gallery relocated in Georgetown to the Glackens House, former home of painter William Glackens. In 1998, Conway opened a second location in Santa Fe, New Mexico. Prior to opening the gallery, Conway ran her own fine arts conservation studio.
The gallery represents modern and contemporary artists including Eric Aho, Will Barnet, Leonard Baskin, Dorothy Dehner, Mary Ellen Doyle, Brece Honeycutt, Ross M. Merrill, Otto and Gertrud Natzler, Sam Scott and Edward Sorel. The gallery is also the sole fine arts representative of sculpture, painting, and drawings by Patrick Oliphant, a Pulitzer Prize winning political cartoonist.
Conditions Governing Access note
Use of original papers requires an appointment.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Susan Conway Gallery records were donated by Susan Conway in 2004 and 2007.
Aho, Eric, 1966-; Barnet, Will, 1911-2012; Baskin, Leonard, 1922-2000; Dehner, Dorothy, 1901-1994; Honeycutt, Brece; Mary Ellen Doyle, 1938-; Merrill, Ross M.; Natzler, Gertrud; Natzler, Otto; Oliphant, Pat, 1935-; Scott, Sam; Sorel, Edward, 1929-; Susan Conway Conservation Studio.; Art galleries, Commercial--Washington (D.C.); Photographs; Visitors' books
- Artists' Files, circa 1928, circa 1940s-2003; Series 1; 7.6 Linear feet Boxes 1-8, 26, OV 27
  Scope and Contents note
  Artists' Files contains a variety of materials documenting the gallery's representation of its artists and their careers. Materials may include biographies, correspondence, exhibition printed materials, price lists, newspaper clippings, notes, photographs and slides, sales invoices, and shipping records. Artists of interest include Eric Aho, Will Barnet, Leonard Baskin, Dorothy Dehner, Mary Ellen Doyle, Brece Honeycutt, Ross M. Merrill, Otto and Gertrud Natzler, Sam Scott and Edward Sorel.
  Arrangement note
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by artist’s last name.
  - Aho, Eric (Box 1)
    - Clients (Apr. 10, 2001), 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - History, 1997-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Letter - Contract, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Sales and Interest, 1999; 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Page, 1997-2000; Includes 1 floppy disk (3.5 inch) (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Andrews, Benny, 1988-1998 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - Anthony, Carol, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Barnet, Will, 1989-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
  - Baskin, Leonard (Box 1)
    - Announcement Cards, 1994-2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - England, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Interview, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Mailing List, 1994-2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Michelson Galleries, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Monumental Woodcuts, Ken Shure (2001), 1994-2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Press Reviews, circa 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Price Lists, circa 1998-2000s (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - Sculpture, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Works Returned, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Berkowitz, Leon, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Blackwell, Patty, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Blackwell, Patty (Box 1)
    - Consignment Agreement, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Press Kit, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Price Lists, 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bluhm, Norman - Inactive, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bogomolov, Gleb, 1988-1989; 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bortz, Julia and Marc Bergerson - Inactive, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bosch, Gerry - Inactive, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Boxer, Stanley, 1998-1999; 1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Brooke, Peter, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Calfee, William, 1995-1997; 1980s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chapin, Francis, 2001; 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - Chapin, Francis - Inactive, 1973; 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chappelear, Larry, 1985-1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chi, Chen, 1978; 1993; undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Christenberry, William, 1996-2003; 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
  - Christenberry, William (Box 2)
    - Atlanta Contemporary Art Center (Mar. 2000), circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Marumoto, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - The Morris Museum, Kevin Grogan, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Clapp, William Henry (Lawrence Jeppson Assoc.) - Inactive, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Clark, Michael - Inactive, 1974; 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Comès, Marcella - Inactive, circa 1940s-1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cooper, Nan - Inactive, 1988-1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cunningham, Francis, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cunningham, Francis - Inactive, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Daumier, Honoré, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Oversized material housed in OV 27
  - Davidoff, Susan, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Day, Horace, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Dehner, Dorothy, circa 1993-2002 (Box 2, Folder 21-22)
  - Dehner, Dorothy (Box 2)
    - Atelier 4 - Wash., D.C. to NYC, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Biography - Special Notes, 1990s-2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - The Columbus Museum (Columbus, GA), 2003; 2001 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Constantine, Mildred, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Conversations With Dehner and Marter Essay, circa 1990s (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Conversations With Joan Marter, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1994; circa 1928 (Box 2, Folder 29-31)
    - Correspondence With Marter and Curators, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Current Inventory, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Fortissimo and Dark Harmony, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Legal/Contracts/Payments, 1996; 2002 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art (NYC), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Museum Interest In, 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Betty Parsons - Notes From Caril Dreyfuss, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Press, 1994-1999 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Prices - History, 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Publicity, 1980-1999 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Stanford University Museum, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The Design Center - Inactive, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
  - The Design Center, Richard Burkett - Inactive, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Downey, Connie, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Doyle, Mary Ellen, 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 48-49)
  - Doyle, Mary Ellen (Box 2)
    - The Albuquerque Museum, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Artex/Storage, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 51-52)
    - ArtNews Ad Responses, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - ArtNews Ad for Sagaponack (2002), 2003 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Doyle, Mary Ellen (Box 3)
    - Clients and Buyers, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Current (2001-2002), 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Exhibitions, 1990-1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Freidenrich, Jill [and Dorothy Dehner], 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - "Horizon" Letters and Catalogs Temporary/Working Info, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Letters/Visuals Sent (Aug. 2002), 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Lynch, Virginia, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
    - Mailing Responses From Museums, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Museum Clients, 1995-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - New Orleans Museum of Art, "September Evening", 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Original Color Transparency for Catalog, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Paste-Up, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Phillips Collection, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - Press Reviews Before 1997, 1980s-1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Price Lists - Old, 1990s (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Publicity, 1990s-2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Ratliff Ads and Announcement Card, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Richardson, Phil, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Sales, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Shipping, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Spokes, Ellen Kutzen, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Traveling Exhibition (1999), 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Dumbacher, Joe, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dunlap, William, Mailing Lists, circa 1998 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Einstein, Ula, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Eisendrath, Mark, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Etherington, Don, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Etherington, Don, Parylene, 1983-2000 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Evans, Mary Page, 1995-2002 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Evans, Mary Page (Box 3)
    - Donation to The National Museum of Women in the Arts, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - The Kennedy Center, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Frederick, Eugene, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Contains original pen and pencil drawings
  - Frederick, Eugene - Inactive, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Gaon, Simon, 1995-1997; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Genn, Roman, 1996-2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Goulet, Lorrie, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Green, Michael - Inactive, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Guberman - Inactive, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Habsburg, Gabriela von, 1998-2002; circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Habsburg, Gabriela von - Inactive, 1984-1998 (Box 4, Folder 6-9)
  - Harkins, George, 1996-2003 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Henenberger, Tracy, 1988-2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Henenberger, Tracy - Inactive, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hildebrand, Sharon, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hilleary, James, 1987-1991; 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hilleary, James, Hilleary and Efron Presentation, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hines, Felrath - Inactive, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Hirsch, Amanda [Original folder was empty], undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hodges, Luther, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Holden, Donald, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Holden, Donald (Box 4)
    - Holden/Moser/Smithsonian American Art Museum, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Letter Sent Sept. 27, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Museums, 1991-2002 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Honeycutt, Brece, 1997-2003 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Jenkins, Henry - Inactive, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Jennings-Offen, Meredith, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Jones, Lou - Inactive, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Kai, Yi, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Kinstler, Everett Raymond, 1987-1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Kinstler, Everett Raymond (Box 4)
    - Biography, 1990s (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Jones, Bill, Portrait, Sea Island, GA, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Kinstler, Everett Raymond (Box 5)
    - Publicity, 1983-2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Visuals, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Kipniss, Robert, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Larson, Blaine (Box 5)
    - Biography, 1970-1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Biography [and Andrew Hudson], 1996; 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Old, 1988-1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Current, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Octagon, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Visuals, 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
  - Latven, Bud, 1993; 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Latven, Bud (Box 5)
    - Inventory, 1998; 1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - List Follow-Up, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Lee, Willis F., 1996-2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Levine, David, 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 15-17)
  - Levine, David (Box 5)
    - Biography and Visuals, 1980s-1990s (Box 5, Folder 18-20)
    - Holiday Show (1998), 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Levine/Johnson, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Lewis, George, 1988-1990; 1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Looper, Willem de, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - MacDonald, Kevin, circa 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Martin, Agnes, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - McBride, Margaret Olney, 1988-2002 (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
  - McBride, Margaret Olney (Box 5)
    - Biography and Press, 1988-1999; Includes one floppy disk (5 inch) (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Biography and Resume, 1990s-2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Publicity, 1982-1999 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - McCarthy, Colleen, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - McKenzie, Mary Beth, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - McKenzie, Mary Beth (Box 5)
    - Biography, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Publicity, 1988-2001 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Merrill, Ross M., 1994-2003 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Merrill, Ross M. (1988), 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Merrill, Ross M. (Box 6)
    - (1994-1995), 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - (1997), 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - (1998), 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Price Lists (2000) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Publicity, circa 1988-1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Moses, Forrest, 1999-2001; 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Moss, Ben Frank, 1989-2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Moss, Ben Frank (March 30, 1999), 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Nurmi, Maritta, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Ogden, Deedy, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Oxman, Katja, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Parker, Robert Andrew, 1995-2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Parker, Robert Andrew, Franz Kafka - dreams, diaries and fragments, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Polan, Annette (Box 6)
    - Biography and PR, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Visuals, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Pousette-Dart, Richard, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Prentice, Elena, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Priest, Ellen, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Qi, Hai-Ping (Beijing), circa 1998 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Randall, Colleen, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Reid, Charles, 1990s-2002 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Rice, Pierce, 1981; 1988-2002 (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
  - Rice, Pierce (Box 6)
    - Biography, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Philip Morris, 1981-1991 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Publicity, 1980s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Visuals, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Rovit, Honey, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Safer, John, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Sanders, Linda, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Schwartz, Daniel Bennett, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Scott, David, 1989-2003 (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
  - Scott, David (Box 6)
    - (2000), 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Clients, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Mailing List, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Resume, circa 2000 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Scott, Sam, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Scott, Sam (Box 6)
    - (Sept. 1999) (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - (2000) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Scott, Sam (Box 7)
    - (2000-2002), circa 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - (2001) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Atelier 4 Pick-up for Philip Palmer, Chicago to S.F., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Biography and PR, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Deck the Walls" Exhibition (Nov. 9, 1999-Jan. 8, 2000), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Deck the Walls" Exhibition, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Gifts From a Winter Garden" Exhibition (Apr. 13-May 8, 1999) (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - La Maison Francaise, Lazare Paupert, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Phillips Collection (2000), 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Une Saison," French Embassy, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Silverman, Burton, 1998-2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Silverman, Burton (Box 7)
    - Publicity, 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - RTA (Feb. 20, 2002) (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Shipment, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Smith, David, 1990s-2000 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
  - Sockwell, Carroll, 1989-1990; 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Sorel, Edward, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Sorel, Edward (Box 7)
    - Biography and Publicity, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1985-2002 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Visuals, 1977-1999 (Box 7, Folder 21-22)
  - Stark, Robert, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Steiner, Peter, 1980s-1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Steiner, Peter, Exhibition (Oct. 6-31, 1992), 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Steinke, Bettina, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Steinke, Bettina, 3 Pastel Drawings, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Stevenson, Brockie, 1986-1996; 1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Stifel, Lida, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Sultan, Donald, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Thompson, Richard, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Thompson, Richard (Box 7)
    - Biography/Resume, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - "Deck the Walls" Exhibition (Dec. 8, 1998-Jan. 9, 1999), 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Exhibition (1997), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - The National Portrait Gallery, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - The National Portrait Gallery, George Washington Drawing, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Publicity, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Varshavskaya, Elena, circa 2000 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Webster, Stokely, 1976-2000 (Box 7, Folder 39-43)
  - Webster, Stokely, circa 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Webster, Stokely, Ad, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, James (Dec. 15, 1999) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wischhusen, Shelly, 1988-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wood, Susan, 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Wood, Susan (Box 8)
    - Publicity, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Visuals, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Wright, Frank, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wright, Michael, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Yang, Ming-Yi and Li Lundin, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 11-12)
  - Yerkes, David, 1988-1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Yerkes, David (Box 8)
    - Biography and Resume, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Publicity, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Yerkes, Sara, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Restricted Folder (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Oversized, Honoré Daumier, 2000 (Box OV 27)
    Oversized material from Box 2, Folder 18
  - Oversized, Lorrie Goulet, 1998 (Box OV 27)
    Oversized material from Box 4, Folder 2
- Client Files, 1987-2003; Series 2; 1.85 Linear feet Boxes 8-10, 26
  This series includes correspondence with individual clients and galleries regarding sales or inquiries, notes, sales invoices, shipping records, and other miscellaneous materials.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by client’s last name or institution’s name.
  - Aiken, Jane, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Alexandre Gallery, Will Barnet's The Caller, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Alexandre Gallery, Will Barnet's The Red Top, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Allied Signal, Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Allin, Mary Ann, Pick-up of Gleb Bogomolov (Aug. 30), 2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - American West Airlines Magazine, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - American Immigration Law Foundation, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Arkansas Arts Center, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Becker, Ron, David Scott, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Ann Beha Architects, Mary Ellen Doyle, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Booth, Tom, Pat Oliphant, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Bradley, David, Office Gallery, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Burka, Mary Ellen Doyle, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Burr, Craig, ArtChicago 2002, Pat Oliphant (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Carey Ellis Company, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Carr, Martha, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Carrington, Alice, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Carrington, Alice, Fernand Léger, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - The Century Association, Jonathan Harding, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Christ Church (Macon, GA), 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Cohen, Barbara, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - The Columbus Museum (Columbus, GA), 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Corn, Wanda, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - The Cummer Gallery of Art, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Currier, Lavinia and Wendy Deal, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Damron, Lawrence, Will Barnet Print, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Deschaises, Arturo, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Dole, Elizabeth, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Doyle, Sandy and Noah, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Ebsworth, Barney, 1999; 1997 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Eisendrath, Charles, 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Eisenstein, Julian, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Elliott, Lee Sullivan, 1998-2002 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Elliott, Sewell, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Evans, Rowland, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 51)